# JACK WITBROCK FINLAY

LOCATION: Melbourne, VIC PHONE: +61 421901993 EMAIL: jack@jackfinlay.com

WEB: jackfinlay.com

### **Career Overview**

Successful career in software development with more than six years of professional experience. Accomplished in scaling and re-engineering of platforms, through .NET, Cloud, and database development. Studying towards a move to a cloud architecture role in the Microsoft Azure ecosystem.

### **Skills**

Programming Languages: C#, SQL, JavaScript

Frameworks: .NET Core & .NET Framework, ASP.NET

Tools: Git, GitHub, Azure DevOps, Visual Studio, Atlassian Jira

**Databases:** SQL Server, CosmosDB **Agile Methodologies:** SCRUM, Kanban

## **Experience**

**Software Developer** Tally Group Ltd, Melbourne, Australia.

April 2020 - Present

- C#, .NET Core, Entity Framework
- Microsoft SQL Server
- Azure cloud App Service, Functions, Durable Functions, Service Bus, Blob and Table storage
- Events and Webhooks

Producing .NET Core solutions for a cloud based utilities billing SaaS platform. Built solution for registration and send of webhooks from an event-driven system using Azure Service Bus, Blob and Table storage, and SQL Server. Design and build of system for importing battery charge/discharge data using Azure Durable Functions.

#### Software Engineer Plexure Group Ltd, Auckland, New Zealand.

January 2019 - April 2020

- C#, .NET Core, .NET Framework
- Microsoft SQL Server, CosmosDB
- Azure cloud App Service, Functions, Service Bus, Notification Hub

Produced .NET Core and Framework solutions on platform optimisation and re-engineering projects. Developed globally reaching products used by over 150 million registered users. Programming in C#, and using Azure cloud platform and technologies.

#### **Software Developer** AlphaCert Labs Ltd, Auckland, New Zealand.

March 2018 - January 2019

- C#, HTML/CSS/JavaScript, ASP.NET MVC with Entity Framework
- Microsoft SQL Server

Full-stack ASP.NET MVC development for investment management software. Primarily C#, HTML/CSS, and JavaScript. ETL and data transformation in C# with MEF. T-SQL database development, database migrations via Fluent Migrator.

#### Analyst Programmer Gentrack Ltd, Auckland, New Zealand.

August 2016 - March 2018

Microsoft SQL Server, Oracle Database development

Defect fixes and extension of functionality of utilities billing software. Data analysis and database development using SQL. Collaboration with internal and external clients to achieve consistent, successful, results and outcomes.

#### **Technical Consultant** Business Mechanix Ltd, Auckland, New Zealand.

April 2015 - August 2016

- C#, HTML/CSS/JavaScript, ASP.NET MVC with Entity Framework
- SPARQL RDF API
- Microsoft SQL Server

Developed a website for international students to find study options in New Zealand. Managed and mentored a team of three interns working over the 2015/16 summer. Setup and managed Azure resources. Maintained and developed C# applications. Ad-hoc customer support.

### Intern Developer University of Auckland IT Services, Auckland, New Zealand.

December 2014 - February 2015

Java, Scriptella, Bash

Developed existing and new projects using Java. Created an HTTP driver for Scriptella, reverse engineered from the source code. Various ad-hoc Scriptella, Groovy and Bash scripts.

### **Education**

### Auckland University of Technology, Auckland, New Zealand

Bachelor of Computer and Information Science - Software Development Major

Topics covered included: Software Development in C# and Java, Object-Oriented Design and Development, Databases, Agile Methodologies, Information security, Data process Modelling, Project Management, Discrete Mathematics and Linear Algebra, Data Structures, and Algorithms.